JUSTIN LIU

justintwd@gmail.com +886-982-612-553 blog.justintw.com

I am a **full-stack web developer and system administrator with 6 years industry and 3 years contract,** specializing in scalable cloud architectures for web application and network maintenance, aiming to become a true software engineer and loves coding a lot. While my work focuses on web engineering, mostly building SPA with front-end framework like Angular, and building RESTful api with back-end framework such as Django or Tornado. For my part-time IT task, I build and maintenance network and various IT service for my company. My non-work interest ranges widely. By spending free time learning other computer science related subjects such as network security and algorithms, my interest into computer just keeps deepening. Building small tools which makes my life easier is also something I love to do on the weekend. I am from Taiwan and looking for engineer positions in Taiwan.

</> </> SKILLS

IT Service (Proficient) Bind 9, Squid 3, Samba, Nginx, OpenLDAP, FreeRadius, Docker, VPN

Network (Proficient) Nmap, Shorewall, tshark, iptables, mtr, dig

Web (Back-end) (Intermediate) Django, Tornado, RabbitMQ, NodeJS, PHP, RESTful, HTTP Protocol

Web (Front-end) (Basic) Angular, React, jQuery, Bootstrap

Database (Basic) MySQL, MongoDB, Redis

Configuration and laaC (Basic) GUN Makefile, Puppet, CloudFormation, Terraform

CI / CD (Proficient) Jenkins, Drone

EMPLOYMENT

Seinor Engineer, IIoT Solution Dept., MOXA Inc.

2018-02 — 2018-06

Design and implement CI/CD flow for IIoT product and maintain web backend project.

- Built various service for develop team: DNS, OpenVPN, CI Build Server, Gitlab
- Design and implement continuous integration and continuous delivery for 75+ software component
- Improve web backend architect for increase support more connection up to 500%

Principal Engineer, CCP Dept., Openfind Information Technology, Inc.

2017-09 — 2018-01

A software developer of enterprise file sync and sharing production.

- . Design and implement of single sign-on feature
- . Design and implement of file access api for third-party partner
- Design and implement of multi-server management feature

Software Engineer, EFSS Dept., Hope Bay Technologies, Inc.

2013-06 — 2017-09

Hope Bay Technologies, Inc. is a startup company since June 2013 owned by Dr. Ben Jai, I involve with building, maintaining network, building various IT service for company, and join many commercial products development.

- Information Systems and Technology
- Built and maintenance of network and service: OpenLDAP, DNS, OpenVPN, NAS, Gitlab, DB Cluster, FreeRaidus
- Built and maintenance of package cache: pypi, docker, npm, dpkg
- Built and maintenance of IT Service: DNS, LDAP, GitLab, DB Cluster, FreeRadius
- Web developer
- Design and implement of Phone Recording System
- Design and implement of IP-PBX Recording System
- Design and implement of Tera Phone Web File Manager
- Design and implement of EFSS Product Web Development

Seinor Engineer, CTBU, Delta Electronics

2012-06 — 2013-06

I am a web application developer for data center physical machine management product.

- Data Center Machine Manager Development Tools: Django, Twitter Bootstrap, jQuery
- File Storage Product Development Tools: PHP, Ext.js

EDUCATION

Master, Graduate Institute of Electronics Engineering, National Taiwan University

2010-09 — 2012-06

Bachelor, Department of EE, National Taiwan University of Science and Technology

2006-09 — 2010-06

WRITING

Justin Tech Share Blog, Justin Liu

2017

An OAuth-based Single Sign-On System for Mobile Applications, Justin Liu

2012

AWARDS